populis.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy | Populis

We, Populis Ireland Limited (“ **Populis** “), are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This privacy policy explains how we use the information we collect about you and how you can instruct us, if you prefer, to limit the use of that information.

  1. **Collection and Use of Information**  
We will obtain personal data about you whenever you complete an online form on the website,[www.populis.com](http://www.populis.com/) (the “ **Site** “) or send an e-mail to us. We will use your personal data for the purposes of responding to, and dealing with, your query or request.By making a query or request, we will collect and store the following data relating to you: 
    1. your full name;
    2. your e-mail and residential address;
    3. your date of birth;
    4. your mobile telephone number, and
    5. your curriculum vitae, including details of past experience and professional and academic background.

We may also collect personal information that we request from you regarding your use of the Site or that we collect automatically about your visit to the Site. Please see our section on  **Use of Cookies**.

We may use aggregate information and statistics for the purposes of monitoring site usage in order to help us develop the Site and may provide such aggregate information to third parties. These statistics will not include information that can be used to identify any individual.

  2. **Access to Personal Information**  
We may provide your personal data to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies and agents for the purpose of responding to your query or request.
  3. **Marketing**  
We will not provide your personal data to third parties for marketing purposes without your consent.
  4. **Sale of Business**  
If Populis is sold or integrated with another business, your details may be disclosed to our advisers and any prospective purchasers and their advisers, and will be passed on to the new owners of Populis.
  5. **Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We may use cookies to store information on your computer. This information may include information relating to your use of the Site, information about your computer such as the computer’s IP address and browser type. We will only read cookies from your cookie file placed there through your web browser’s interaction with the Site. Note that you may change your browser settings to refuse cookies.
  6. **Updating your Details**  
If any of the information that you have provided to Populis changes, for example if you change your e-mail address, you can contact us by e-mail at [insert email]. You have a right to request a copy of the personal data we hold about you (for which we may charge a small fee) and to correct any inaccuracies in your information.
  7. **Changes**  
If we change our privacy policy we will post the changes on this page, and may place notices on other pages of the Site, so that you may be aware of the information we collect and how we use it at all times. Your continued use of the Site will signify that you agree to any such changes.
  8. **Contact Details**  
We welcome your views about our Site and our privacy policy. If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact us by e-mail at [info@populis.com](mailto:info@populis.com).
